

CONTACT

- (+91) 8475962723
- New Ashok Nagar (New Delhi), INDIA
- mindgo.sharma@gmail.com
- -5 Years 2 Months of experience

EDUCATION

2017

B.Tech/B.E. - Computers

Uttarakhand Technical University College of Engineering Roorkee

Grade - 70%

2012

XIIth

Bihar, English Marks - 70-74.9%

2009

Xth

Bihar, English Marks - 70-74.9%

KEYSKILLS

AMAN SHARMA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT ENGINEER-II

PROFILE SUMMARY

IMMEDIATE JOINER

Having overall and react-native working experience of around 5 yrs, I'm looking forward to an opportunity to work in a dynamic environment where I can utilize my skills for developing my career and for the growth of the organization.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 -2024 Software Development Engineer-

Cardekho Group

I am working as Software Development Engineer-II, Develop Cross Platform App(iOS & Android).

2020 -2022

Software Engineer New Media Guru Pvt Ltd

I am working as Software Engineer, Develop Cross Platform App(iOS & Android)

2019 -2020

Software Engineer Affle

I was working as Software Engineer, Develop Cross Platform App(iOS & Android). React Hooks

React.js

Javascript

React-native

Redux

HTML

Context API

Firebase

CSS

Push Notification

JIRA Tool

Higher Order Component(HOC)

Render Props

LANGUAGE

HINDI

ENGLISH

BHOJPURI

SOCIAL LINKS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aman-sharma-5475901ba/

PROJECTS

LMS

799 Days

It's app for both the platform(Android & iOS) to create leads and manage leads of new car purchase in South East Asia.

SFA

799 Days

It's app for both the platform(Android & iOS) for managing loan and insurance of used car in South East Asia.

Dealer App

799 Days

It's app for both the platform(Android & iOS) for managing dealer in South East Asia.

Wealth Concert

1103 Days

It's app for both the platform(Android & iOS) for creating committee and fund distribution online.

Vouch

120 Days

It's app for both the platform(Android & iOS) to create and share feed like Instagram.

Niine

92 Days

It's a Mobile application for both the platform(Android & iOS), in this girls or women can track their next period date by logging their previous date and can also find their ovulation period.

Sunny E-Store

92 Days

It's a E-Commerce Mobile Application for both the platform(Android & iOS), sells electronic gadgets.

Funda E-Learning

365 Days

It's an mediators app for both the platform(Android & iOS) between tutor and



student, in this app student can book their sessions for resolving doubts and tutor can place bid to their respective sessions.